<Computer id="NHCross" name="NightHawks' Crossroads" ip="25.187.106.244" security="5" type="4">
<adminPass pass="Sl1ckPr3y" />
<trace time="-1" />
<admin type="progress"/>
<file path="home/Project_Oblivion" name="GOALS.txt">Target: Allan Turner

1) SEND Allan's Med File to the RAPTOR@jmail.com (Gain access to the medical archive and search for his entry)
2) WIPE OFF Allan's degrees (Gain access to the academical archive and search for his entry)</file>
<file path="home/Project_Oblivion/Medical_part" name="Details.txt">I know an address of the server but you can't get in that simply, they have a special port Num. 104, and obviously nobody left admin's password for you.

You have to find either a password, either a port breaker. All I could find is a PC of one doctor. These folks work with that archive regularly, you'll most probably find some entry point there, use some social engeniering.

Archive: 102.36.38.173
Doctor: 221.214.78.150</file>
<file path="home/Project_Oblivion/Academical_part" name="Details.txt">This one gets tricky, because I have no fucking idea where to look.

Actually, there is one lead, though might sound weird. I know a guy who know a guy who got kicked out off the university recently. Luckily, it is the same one Allan finished, and it is connected to the International Academic Database. Gain access through that dropout kid, he supposed to contact university staff

Lead:178.184.180.189</file>
<file path="home/Oath" name="Oath.txt">I am acknowledging next rules and will obey them:

I will always evolve and try to become stronger and powerful in all life's aspects

Morality is a codex of weak people to make everyone equally weak as well, and if that stands on my way of getting more powerful, I will ignore it

There is no mercy to the weak people, because they could stay strong, but preferred opposite, and as honorable agent of fate, I swear to utilize such individuals as tools or react to them as a trash

If I have a choice between weakness and death, death is the only way, because I will die strong and independent, and won't live a miserable life as a slave</file>
<file path="home/Memory_Tools" name="Memo.txt">Attention to NightHawks!

This set of memory-sensitive software is used to extract dumps from all kind of machines. Use this to get a piece of data and analyze it, so it can be restored after deletion procedure</file>
<file path="home/Memory_Tools" name="MemDumpGenerator.exe">#MEM_DUMP_GENERATOR#</file>
<file path="home/Memory_Tools" name="MemForensics.exe">#MEM_FORENSICS_EXE#</file>
<file path="home/Misc" name="PD list">This is a part of a list of Police Departments of California State

Be careful and remember their addresses, so you can identify them properly if you found them in any logs:

46.55.180.122 (San-Francisco)
250.224.135.131 (Los-Angeles)
135.133.244.178 (San-Diego)
17.136.34.154 (Sacramento)
175.102.196.84 (Santa-Rosa)
215.191.241.195 (Fresno)
243.157.218.48 (San-Jose)</file>
<Memory>
	<Data>
		<Block>
			IRC DUMP HAVE BEEN RELOCATED HERE DUE TO PROXY INSTABILITY
				
Maverick: Did you investigate those police servers?
				
Jester: Yes, they are being renovated by EnTech I presume, 
they have fancy whitelists and other extreme security measures
				
Maverick: We could profit from their Asset servers
				
Jester: They are unreachable, at least for now
				
Jester: Also, you should tell everyone to be careful, 
there was a nasty story recently, involving some of these PD servers
				
Maverick: Speak
				
Jester: All listed servers, except Santa-Rosa are renovated, 
I think it is a matter of time when Santa-Rosa gonna join EnTech's "Enrichment Program"
				
Jester: Meaning Santa-Rosa is still vulnerable 
And they don't have new scanning systems as well
				
Maverick: So they are outsiders for now?
				
Jester: I wouldn't say it that way, we made a little test last month 
and we dropped dirty netcfgx.dll from a test machine
				
Jester: They seem to retransmit it to somewhere else
				
Jester: Thing is, cops arrived in a 52 minutes
				
Maverick: Ah shit, here we go again
				
Jester: As long as we staying away from them, I don't think they'll locate us
				
Maverick: I'll ring some bells to find out what we can do about it, 
maybe we should disrupt their transmitter
				
Maverick: As for now, we are going dark...
				
			END OF IRC DUMP
		</Block>
		<Block>
			IRC DUMP HAVE BEEN RELOCATED HERE DUE TO PROXY INSTABILITY
			
Jester: Jenkins, I fucking tired of it, 
When you will learn how to use a fucking erase-script properly?
I am tired of sending your tools over and over again after your unsuccesful experiments
				
Jester: Here is your fucking WebWorm
				
Jester: !ATTACHMENT:link#%#文件存放节点#%#212.42.92.36
				
			END OF IRC DUMP
		</Block>
	</Data>
</Memory>
</Computer>