<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<mission id="M8 2">
  <goals>
  <goal type="fileupload" target="C2B" file="Plans.docx" path="home/Personal" destTarget="C2C" destPath="Drop/Uploads"/>
  <goal type="fileupload" target="C2B" file="Poses.png" path="home/Personal" destTarget="C2C" destPath="Drop/Uploads"/>
  <goal type="fileupload" target="C2B" file="Notes.docx" path="home/Personal" destTarget="C2C" destPath="Drop/Uploads"/>
  <goal type="fileupload" target="NHCross" file="Kati_25_11_19.png" path="home/Contract_Files/Denigration" destTarget="C2A" destPath="home"/>
  </goals>
  <missionStart val="0">loadConditionalActions:Actions/Act 2/Mission 8/C2.xml</missionStart>
  <missionEnd val="1">addRankSilent</missionEnd>
  <nextMission>NONE</nextMission>
  
  <posting title="Denigration">
One excentric politician is not intimidated with my blackmail, it is time to fix this
  </posting>
  <email>
    <sender>E-Mail</sender>
    <subject>Denigration</subject>
    <body>此电子邮件是由从外部收件箱接收：

Greetings, I am Oswaldo, blackmail is my purpose of life and main line of work. I have a trouble with one polititian, name is J.J. Broadster, and I have some juicy photos of him and 19-y/o Kati, practising some BDSM, usual stuff I get on guys like him. Nobody will see these photos if he resign from his counselor post.

Thing is, he think it is not a big problem for him and nobody would care about that. But hey, everybody loves some sex scandals, but definitely not female victims. So if I can't directly influence him, I need you to show Kati what can in theory make her a star of the academy. Place my photos on her PC (Link will be provided), You can find them on your organisation's Crossroads Server. Maybe she can motivate him better.

And in the process, I need some fresh material that I can use. Get inside his PC as well and get anything personal and preferably dirty, then drop it on my Drop Server that I will provide.

目标:

1) UPLOAD dirty photos on Kati's PC (Place them in /home folder)
2) UPLOAD all personal data of Broadster to Oswaldo's Drop Server
3) REPLY to this E-Mail after everything is done
</body>
    <attachments>
	<link comp="C2A" />
	<link comp="C2B" />
	<link comp="C2C" />
    </attachments>
  </email>
</mission>