<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<mission id="Mission 1 Route A">
  <goals>
    <!-- Goals here -->
	<goal type="fileupload" target="M1rA_SK" file="netcfgx.dll" path="sys" destTarget="PDAsset" destPath="Drop/Uploads"/>
	<goal type="filechange" target="M1rA_Sec" file="Presentation_Text.docx" path="home" keyword="DICK" removal="true"/>
	<goal type="filechange" target="M1rA_Sec" file="Presentation_Text.docx" path="home" keyword="ePhone" caseSensitive="true"/>
  </goals>
  <missionStart val="0">loadConditionalActions:Actions/Act 1/Mission 1/rA Actions.xml</missionStart>
  <missionEnd val="0">loadConditionalActions:Actions/Act 1/Mission 1/Link.xml</missionEnd>
  <nextMission>NONE</nextMission>
  <posting title="Cybervandalizm">
  
  
  
Some trickster tried to have some fun with confidential promotion documents, now they are in mess, word DICK is everywhere!

But what's more important - this is a text for new ePhone presentation. We have to fix everything and find a guy's IP, before the whole world would know how much SFCPD suck
  </posting>
  <email>
	<sender>Clara</sender>
	<subject>Good vandal = locked up vandal</subject>
	<body>
I knew you would pick up that mission. Me and Javis will cover the rest two.

Security Chief of the Pear company texted us with this news. He said it wouldn't be a problem for him, but there is just too little time left before presentation.

Sooo he left everything as it is, which means most probably you will find some tracks of that script kiddie.

I want his netcfgx.dll, you can find it in sys/, so we could research every other sin he made and then pack him up. When you get it, upload it to the Asset server's upload module.

Oh, and by the way, could you also replace DICK back to ePhone in the presentation file? Pretty please? You will find it with the logs and everything on PC that I linked.

-C

PRO TIP:
Use LOGS to find tracks of criminal's computer systems

GOALS:
1)GET INSIDE vandal's 战机 and UPLOAD his netcfgx.dll to the ASSET server's upload dropbox
2)REPLACE word "DICK" to "ePhone" in presentation file</body>
	<attachments>
	<link comp="M1rA_Sec"/>
	<account comp="M1rA_Sec" user="admin" pass="JeveStobs"/>
	</attachments>
</email>
</mission>